

Hunter Warren

hunterwarren.u

hunter.warren@gmail.com

512.557.5032

About Me

I'm a PHP / JavaScript full-stack web developer transitioning to programming after 7+ years experience as an Advertising Art Director /Designer. What excites me about programming is the potential to make people's lives easier and better through technology, and provide them with value they never expected. Currently working on a multiple crypto-to-fiat currency converter to gain better understanding of available crypto APIs.

SKILLS:

Programming

Software

Professional/Interpersonal

- PHP / Laravel
- MySQL
- JavaScript / jQuery / AJAX
- CSS / Bootstrap
- HTML

- Photoshop, Illustrator, inDesign, After Effects, Premiere, Audition
- Excel, Google Sheets
- Powerpoint, Keynote
- Visual design and mass communication sensibilites
- Presentation experience
- Familiar with giving / receiving constructive feedback, and team collaboration

PROJECTS:

OldLister

Reddit.dev

Globetrotter.pro

Using vanilla PHP, MySQL, HTML and custom CSS, we created an online community/ classifieds website that allows account holders to buy and sell goods, while allowing anyone to browse what's for sale. Using a Laravel framework, we built an analogue to the famous 'front page of the internet' that usesMySQL to store user info, votes and content, and PHP to allow voting, ranking, and posting.

A mobile-responsive app for travel budgeting. Built with Laravel, we use PHP to call an API with cost data from 30,00 locations. User budgets are built with a jQuery and JavaScript 'wizard' and stored in a MySQL database, which is managed with Laravel.

WORK:

Previous Experience

2014-2017

Art Director at DDB New York

Digital, Social, Video and 360 advertising campaign work for Clean & Clear, State Farm, Frigidaire, Electrolux, Lipton, Breyers, Exxon Mobil, and Royal Canin. Also responsible for digital content creation / content optimization.

2012-2014

Interactive Designer at DDB New York

Design work and UI /UX on mobile and desktop sites, and digital ads for: Frigidaire, Electrolux, State Farm, Reebok, USTA, RoC Skin Care, Aveeno, Lipton. Worked with developers to guide translation from design into digital product.

2011-2012

Graphic Designer at Imagemme, Inc.

Created logos, identity work, websites, UI/UX, packaging, digital work and print materials. Additional duties: customer contact/relations, print/materials sourcing, creating mockups, on-site installations, and press checks.

Education

SUMMER 2017

CODEUP

Completed 16-week software development immersive in San Antonio, consisting of 536+ hours of curriculum covering full-stack web development and associated technologies. Built various programming projects alone and in teams.

2007-2010

TEXAS STATE UNIVERSITY

San Marcos, TX. BFA Communication Design. Summa Cum Laude.